[
    {
        "question": "I like - I like music that goes like this: 'falalala!'. But sometimes I like - I like music that goes like this: 'FALALALA'!",
        "choice1": "Fred Fredburger",
        "choice2": "Jolly Roger",
        "choice3": "Flapjack",
        "choice4": "Gunter",
        "answer": 1
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Chowder, if there's one thing mother's taught me it's to sleep as much as you can. That way you don't have to face the horrible reality of what your life's become.",
        "choice1": "Eduardo",
        "choice2": "Raj",
        "choice3": "Gazpacho",
        "choice4": "Wendell Feinstein",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "You said, uh ... 'libation', or something... juicebox?",
        "choice1": "Barry Mackerbacker",
        "choice2": "Alan Keane",
        "choice3": "Jackie Khones",
        "choice4": "Mr. Green",
        "answer": 3
    },
    
    {
        "question": "GET OFFA MY PROPERTY!",
        "choice1": "Wendell Feinstein",
        "choice2": "Sticky Beard",
        "choice3": "Sloppy Moe",
        "choice4": "Fuzzy Lumpkins",
        "answer": 4
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Watch where you're goin', ya fool!",
        "choice1": "Raja Jaja",
        "choice2": "Di Lung",
        "choice3": "Hak Foo",
        "choice4": "Kanojo Cho",
        "answer": 2
    },
    
    {
        "question": "New dog belongs to Soto. You go now!",
        "choice1": "Azmuth",
        "choice2": "Aku",
        "choice3": "Cinderblock",
        "choice4": "Soto",
        "answer": 4
    },
    
    {
        "question": "*pants*",
        "choice1": "Soto's dog",
        "choice2": "Courage",
        "choice3": "Ren",
        "choice4": "Saliva",
        "answer": 4
    },
    
    {
        "question": "It's a delicious midst of Purple Flurp",
        "choice1": "A.J.",
        "choice2": "Chad Dickson",
        "choice3": "Ike Wilderman",
        "choice4": "Lenny Baxter",
        "answer": 3
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Go through that. You're so close, you have to keep going.",
        "choice1": "Aelita",
        "choice2": "Sapna Nehru",
        "choice3": "Ashi",
        "choice4": "Kimiko Tohomiko",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "bah-gawk!",
        "choice1": "Chicken",
        "choice2": "Bridget",
        "choice3": "Gertrude",
        "choice4": "Lazar",
        "answer": 2
    }
]